[{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663911183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10545,"timeElapsed":61686},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663922081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":10897,"timeElapsed":72584},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663951264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":29181,"timeElapsed":101767},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663955481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4215,"timeElapsed":105984},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663960032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":110535},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663966098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6065,"timeElapsed":116601},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663968798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2698,"timeElapsed":119301},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735663986032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":17232,"timeElapsed":136535},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664012590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":26581,"timeElapsed":163093},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664033132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":19299,"timeElapsed":183634},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664039514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6382,"timeElapsed":190017},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664044580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5065,"timeElapsed":195083},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664049463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4881,"timeElapsed":199966},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664052146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":202649},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664054979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2832,"timeElapsed":205482},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664058479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3499,"timeElapsed":208982},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664096462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":37982,"timeElapsed":246964},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664132343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":35881,"timeElapsed":282846},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664167260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":30899,"timeElapsed":317763},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664171493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4232,"timeElapsed":321996},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":18349,"timeElapsed":340346},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664192810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2966,"timeElapsed":343313},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2482,"timeElapsed":345797},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7481,"timeElapsed":353280},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2565,"timeElapsed":355847},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4264,"timeElapsed":360113},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3681,"timeElapsed":363795},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":56732,"timeElapsed":427129},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664280142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3515,"timeElapsed":430645},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9015,"timeElapsed":439662},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":444095},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664296425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2832,"timeElapsed":446928},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":23615,"timeElapsed":470545},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3132,"timeElapsed":473678},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":477728},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3849,"timeElapsed":481578},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7280,"timeElapsed":489878},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2598,"timeElapsed":492477},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664344575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":495077},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664347690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3114,"timeElapsed":498193},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2366,"timeElapsed":500561},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664352158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2098,"timeElapsed":502661},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2582,"timeElapsed":505244},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5981,"timeElapsed":511227},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2048,"timeElapsed":513276},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":14115,"timeElapsed":528927},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2814,"timeElapsed":531744},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":10665,"timeElapsed":542410},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":544610},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664398124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4015,"timeElapsed":548627},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1982,"timeElapsed":550610},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1682,"timeElapsed":552294},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664411440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9648,"timeElapsed":561943},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":564160},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664420240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5464,"timeElapsed":570742},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":572993},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":576126},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1965,"timeElapsed":578093},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2248,"timeElapsed":580343},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":582193},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2164,"timeElapsed":584360},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":586976},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664439323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2849,"timeElapsed":589826},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664447955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7581,"timeElapsed":598458},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664451056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":601559},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":604309},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2298,"timeElapsed":606609},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":609626},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664461106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1981,"timeElapsed":611609},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664468873,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7765,"timeElapsed":619376},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664471723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2848,"timeElapsed":622226},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664476589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4865,"timeElapsed":627092},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":628942},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664496039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":16448,"timeElapsed":646542},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664501105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5065,"timeElapsed":651608},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":12414,"timeElapsed":664024},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664516372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2850,"timeElapsed":666875},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2365,"timeElapsed":669242},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1998,"timeElapsed":671241},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2098,"timeElapsed":673341},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664526639,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3798,"timeElapsed":677141},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3780,"timeElapsed":680924},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3133,"timeElapsed":684058},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664542054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7263,"timeElapsed":692557},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664544488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2433,"timeElapsed":694991},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664547122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":697625},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664549271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":699774},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664551988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2714,"timeElapsed":702491},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664554271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2281,"timeElapsed":704774},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664556588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":707091},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664561771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5181,"timeElapsed":712274},{"subjectID":"5sb5nl93ne","prolificID":"5fb757520b48c928a9b6e00b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677420dbb19b119861c71978","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664565638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"134","question":"When was the last time you walked for more than an hour? Describe where you went and what you saw.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3865,"timeElapsed":716141}]